[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Who was the author of the famous storybook 'Alice's Adventures in Wonderland'?",
    "option1": "Rudyard Kipling",
    "option2": "John Keats",
    "option3": "Lewis Carroll",
    "option4": "H G Wells",
    "answer": "Lewis Carroll"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "Who wrote 'Where ignorance is bliss, it is folly to be wise'?",
    "option1": "Browning",
    "option2": "Marx",
    "option3": "Shakespeare",
    "option4": "Kipling",
    "answer": "Shakespeare"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Which is the first Harry Potter book?",
    "option1": "Goblet of Fire",
    "option2": "Chamber of Secrets",
    "option3": "Philosopher's Stone",
    "option4": "Order of the Phoenix",
    "answer": "Philosopher's Stone"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Jane Eyre' was written by which Bronte sister?",
    "option1": "Anne",
    "option2": "Charlotte",
    "option3": "Emily",
    "option4": "None of these",
    "answer": "Charlotte"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "In the book ‘the Lord of the Rings ‘, who or what is Bilbo?",
    "option1": "Dwarf",
    "option2": "Wizard",
    "option3": "Hobbit",
    "option4": "Troll",
    "answer": "Hobbit"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Mr. and Mrs. Dursley, of number four Privet Drive, were proud to say that they were perfectly normal, thank you very much.\" Which book is this the opening line of?",
    "option1": "Goblet of Fire",
    "option2": "Chamber of Secrets",
    "option3": "Philosopher's Stone",
    "option4": "Order of the Phoenix",
    "answer": "Philosopher's Stone"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What nationality is Gabriel Garcia Marquez?",
    "option1": "Argentina",
    "option2": "Brazil",
    "option3": "Colombia",
    "option4": "Djibouti",
    "answer": "Colombia"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What wasn't written by Shakespeare?",
    "option1": "Romeo and Juliet",
    "option2": "King Lear",
    "option3": "Hamlet",
    "option4": "Ulysses",
    "answer": "Ulysses"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Which poem was writtem in blind condition?",
    "option1": "A Psalm of Life",
    "option2": "Daffodils",
    "option3": "Paradise Lost",
    "option4": "Sonnet 18",
    "answer": "Paradise Lost"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Who was William Shakespeare's wife?",
    "option1": "Anne Hathaway",
    "option2": "Charlotte Bronte",
    "option3": "Jane Austen",
    "option4": "Virginia Woolf",
    "answer": "Anne Hathaway"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "Pride and Prejudice was written by",
    "option1": "Anne Hathaway",
    "option2": "Charlotte Bronte",
    "option3": "Jane Austen",
    "option4": "Virginia Woolf",
    "answer": "Jane Austen"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "Which of these isn't George Orwell's books?",
    "option1": 1984,
    "option2": "Animal Farm",
    "option3": "Homage to Catalonia",
    "option4": "Treasure Island",
    "answer": "Treasure Island"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "Gabriel Garcia Marquez wrote One Hundred Years of",
    "option1": "Adventure",
    "option2": "Revolution",
    "option3": "Silence",
    "option4": "Solitude",
    "answer": "Solitude"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "Fyodor Dostoyevsky didn't write",
    "option1": "Anna Karenina",
    "option2": "Crime and Punishment",
    "option3": "The Brothers Karamazov",
    "option4": "The Idiot",
    "answer": "Anna Karenina"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "Who is not the character of Arabian nights?",
    "option1": "Aladdin",
    "option2": "Ali Baba",
    "option3": "Javed",
    "option4": "Sinbad",
    "answer": "Javed"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "Vladimir Nabokov wrote",
    "option1": "Anita",
    "option2": "Elizabeth",
    "option3": "Lolita",
    "option4": "Mona Lisa",
    "answer": "Lolita"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "Which spanish writer wrote Don Quixote",
    "option1": "Federico Garcia Lorca",
    "option2": "Miguel De Cervantes",
    "option3": "Camilo Jose Cela",
    "option4": "Carlos Ruiz Zafon",
    "answer": "Miguel De Cervantes"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "In Charles Dickens' A Tale of Two Cities, one city is London and another is",
    "option1": "Glasgow",
    "option2": "Cardiff",
    "option3": "New York",
    "option4": "Paris",
    "answer": "Paris"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "The Old Man and the Sea was written by",
    "option1": "Edgar Allan Poe",
    "option2": "Ernest Hemingway",
    "option3": "Mark Twain",
    "option4": "William Faulkner",
    "answer": "Ernest Hemingway"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "The Adventures of Huckleberry Finn adn Tom Sawyer was written by",
    "option1": "Edgar Allan Poe",
    "option2": "Ernest Hemingway",
    "option3": "Mark Twain",
    "option4": "William Faulkner",
    "answer": "Mark Twain"
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "Which of these books were not written by Leo Tolstoy?",
    "option1": "Anna Karenina",
    "option2": "Resurrection",
    "option3": "The Master and Margarita",
    "option4": "War and Peace",
    "answer": "War and Peace"
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "Gabriel Garcia Marquez wrote Love in the Time of",
    "option1": "Cholera",
    "option2": "Fever",
    "option3": "Flu",
    "option4": "Malaria",
    "answer": "Cholera"
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "The Sound and the Fury was written by",
    "option1": "Edgar Allan Poe",
    "option2": "Ernest Hemingway",
    "option3": "Mark Twain",
    "option4": "William Faulkner",
    "answer": "William Faulkner"
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "The Tell-Tale Heart was written by",
    "option1": "Edgar Allan Poe",
    "option2": "Ernest Hemingway",
    "option3": "Mark Twain",
    "option4": "William Faulkner",
    "answer": "Edgar Allan Poe"
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "George Eliot wrote",
    "option1": "Autumn",
    "option2": "Middlemarch",
    "option3": "Mid-April",
    "option4": "Mid-Summer",
    "answer": "Middlemarch"
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "Which indian writer wrote \"The God of Small Things\"?",
    "option1": "Arundhati Roy",
    "option2": "Salman Rushdie",
    "option3": "RK Narayan",
    "option4": "Rabindranath Tagore",
    "answer": "Arundhati Roy"
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "Which of these is not Khaled Hosseini books?",
    "option1": "A Thousand Splendid Suns",
    "option2": "And The Mountains Echoed",
    "option3": "The Kite Runner",
    "option4": "The White Tiger",
    "answer": "The White Tiger"
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "Who wrote Midnight Children?",
    "option1": "Salman Rushdie",
    "option2": "Jhumpa Lahiri",
    "option3": "Vikram Seth",
    "option4": "RK Narayan",
    "answer": "Salman Rushdie"
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "Who wrote Interpreter of Maladies?",
    "option1": "Salman Rushdie",
    "option2": "Jhumpa Lahiri",
    "option3": "Vikram Seth",
    "option4": "RK Narayan",
    "answer": "Jhumpa Lahiri"
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "Who wrote The Namesake?",
    "option1": "Salman Rushdie",
    "option2": "Jhumpa Lahiri",
    "option3": "Vikram Seth",
    "option4": "RK Narayan",
    "answer": "Jhumpa Lahiri"
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "Who wrote A Suitable Boy?",
    "option1": "Salman Rushdie",
    "option2": "Jhumpa Lahiri",
    "option3": "Vikram Seth",
    "option4": "RK Narayan",
    "answer": "Vikram Seth"
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "question": "Who wrote Malgudi Days?",
    "option1": "Salman Rushdie",
    "option2": "Jhumpa Lahiri",
    "option3": "Vikram Seth",
    "option4": "RK Narayan",
    "answer": "RK Narayan"
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "question": "Who wrote Godaan?",
    "option1": "Dhanpat Das",
    "option2": "Gopal Sharma",
    "option3": "Prem Das",
    "option4": "Munshi Premchand",
    "answer": "Munshi Premchand"
  },
  {
    "id": 34,
    "question": "Who wrote national anthem of Bangladesh 'Amar Shonar Bangla'?",
    "option1": "Kazi Nazrul Islam",
    "option2": "Michael Madhusudan Dutt",
    "option3": "Faraaz Kazi",
    "option4": "Rabindranath Tagore",
    "answer": "Rabindranath Tagore"
  },
  {
    "id": 35,
    "question": "My Experiments with Truth' was written by",
    "option1": "APJ Abdul Kalam",
    "option2": "Nirad Chaudhuri",
    "option3": "Mahatma Gandhi",
    "option4": "Jawaharlal Nehru",
    "answer": "Mahatma Gandhi"
  },
  {
    "id": 36,
    "question": "Wings of Fire is an autobiography of",
    "option1": "APJ Abdul Kalam",
    "option2": "Nirad Chaudhuri",
    "option3": "Mahatma Gandhi",
    "option4": "Jawaharlal Nehru",
    "answer": "APJ Abdul Kalam"
  },
  {
    "id": 37,
    "question": "Great poet of Sanskrit",
    "option1": "Tulsidas",
    "option2": "Valmiki",
    "option3": "Kalidasa",
    "option4": "None of these",
    "answer": "Kalidasa"
  },
  {
    "id": 38,
    "question": "Nepali Mahakavi",
    "option1": "Laxmi Prasad Devkota",
    "option2": "Bhanu Bhakta Acharya",
    "option3": "Madhav Prasad Ghimire",
    "option4": "Siddhicharan Shrestha",
    "answer": "Laxmi Prasad Devkota"
  },
  {
    "id": 39,
    "question": "Nepali Adikavi",
    "option1": "Laxmi Prasad Devkota",
    "option2": "Bhanu Bhakta Acharya",
    "option3": "Madhav Prasad Ghimire",
    "option4": "Siddhicharan Shrestha",
    "answer": "Bhanu Bhakta Acharya"
  },
  {
    "id": 40,
    "question": "Nepali Rashtrakavi",
    "option1": "Laxmi Prasad Devkota",
    "option2": "Bhanu Bhakta Acharya",
    "option3": "Madhav Prasad Ghimire",
    "option4": "Siddhicharan Shrestha",
    "answer": "Madhav Prasad Ghimire"
  },
  {
    "id": 41,
    "question": "Nepali Yugakavi",
    "option1": "Laxmi Prasad Devkota",
    "option2": "Bhanu Bhakta Acharya",
    "option3": "Madhav Prasad Ghimire",
    "option4": "Siddhicharan Shrestha",
    "answer": "Siddhicharan Shrestha"
  },
  {
    "id": 42,
    "question": "Nepali Yuwakavi",
    "option1": "Lekhnath Paudel",
    "option2": "Gopal Prasad Rimal",
    "option3": "Motiram Bhatta",
    "option4": "Bhim Nidhi Timari",
    "answer": "Motiram Bhatta"
  },
  {
    "id": 43,
    "question": "Nepali Kabi Shiromani",
    "option1": "Lekhnath Paudel",
    "option2": "Gopal Prasad Rimal",
    "option3": "Motiram Bhatta",
    "option4": "Bhim Nidhi Timari",
    "answer": "Lekhnath Paudel"
  },
  {
    "id": 44,
    "question": "Who wrote National anthem of Nepal \"Sayau Thunga Fulka",
    "option1": "Bishnu Majhi",
    "option2": "Byakul Maila",
    "option3": "Muna Thapa Magar",
    "option4": "None of these",
    "answer": "Byakul Maila"
  },
  {
    "id": 45,
    "question": "Amar Neupane wrote",
    "option1": "Seto Dharti",
    "option2": "Karnali Blues",
    "option3": "Shirishko Phul",
    "option4": "Seto Bagh",
    "answer": "Seto Dharti"
  },
  {
    "id": 46,
    "question": "Buddhisagar wrote",
    "option1": "Seto Dharti",
    "option2": "Karnali Blues",
    "option3": "Shirishko Phul",
    "option4": "Seto Bagh",
    "answer": "Karnali Blues"
  },
  {
    "id": 47,
    "question": "Parijat wrote",
    "option1": "Seto Dharti",
    "option2": "Karnali Blues",
    "option3": "Shirishko Phul",
    "option4": "Seto Bagh",
    "answer": "Shirishko Phul"
  },
  {
    "id": 48,
    "question": "Diamond Shumsher Rana wrote",
    "option1": "Seto Dharti",
    "option2": "Karnali Blues",
    "option3": "Shirishko Phul",
    "option4": "Seto Bagh",
    "answer": "Seto Bagh"
  },
  {
    "id": 49,
    "question": "Krishna Dharawasi did not write",
    "option1": "Adha Bato",
    "option2": "Jhola",
    "option3": "Radha",
    "option4": "Raktakunda",
    "answer": "Raktakunda"
  },
  {
    "id": 50,
    "question": "Blue Mimosa is english translation of",
    "option1": "Seto Dharti",
    "option2": "Karnali Blues",
    "option3": "Shirishko Phul",
    "option4": "Seto Bagh",
    "answer": "Shirishko Phul"
  }
]